LUCIA SEOANE TORREALBA

Digital Marketing Strategist

Buenos Aires, Argentina +54 9 11 30948276 luseoane.t@gmail.com



I am a self-driven entrepreneur with long term experience in creating engaging brands with authentic voice and purpose. On this path, I have designed marketing strategies driving results for diverse projects. Constant learning has been key to coming up with creative and updated solutions for business problems, which is why, I'm always studying and analyzing what I do. I am highly meticulous and organized, and very persistent and enthusiastic towards achieving team goals.

LANGUAGES

English

Perfect

Spanish Native

Portuguese

Advanced

French

Basic, in progress

SKILLS

Photoshop

Advanced

Corel Draw

Advanced

Premiere Pro

Advanced

Illustrator

Basic, in progress.

CERTIFICATIONS

Brother Buenos Aires I August 2021 Award winning School of the year at Cannes Lions **Creative Strategist Certified**

Hubspot Academy I September 2021
Social Media Strategy, In progress
Inbound Marketing Certified
Email Marketing Certified

Simplilearn | August 2021 Digital Analytics Course by Stephan Amel Advanced Web Analytics Certified

EDUCATION

Centro de Investigación Cinematográfica | 2012 College Graduate Filmmaker

ORT I 2008

Industrial Design Highschool Graduate

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Page 2

LUCIA SEOANE TORREALBA

Digital Marketing Strategist

Behance Portfolio Linked-In Profile



FREE-LANCE

Argentina | 2020-2021

Digital Marketing

Consultant

VOLUNTEER

Brasil I 2017
Permacultura Aboré
Natural Builder
Permaculturer
Photographer
Graphic Designer

Colombia I 2015 Mundo Nuevo **Organic Gardener Photographer**

Argentina I 2008-2012 Low-income Neighbourhoods **Tutor I Team Leader** Recreational Workshops Sex Education Workshops

PROJECTS AND EXPERIENCE

Inawake I Argentina I 2021- Today
Athleisure Clothing - Re-branding work in progress
Digital Marketing Strategist
Copywriter I Graphic Designer

Reserva Natural Ouroborus I Costa Rica I 2017-2020
Wildlife Reserve and Sustainability & Permaculture School
Project and Brand Developer
Content Creator I Copywriter
Graphic Designer I Photographer

Galilea Gastronomía I Argentina I 2016-2017 Vegan and Sustainable Food Services

Project and Brand Developer I Copywriter Social Media Marketer I Content Creator Graphic Designer I Photographer

La Vuelta al Mundo I Brasil I Colombia I 2014-2016 Video & Photography for Tourism Project and Brand Developer Marketing Strategist I Community Manager Photographer I Videographer

CLICK TO SEE MY WORK

Inawake Selva de Agua Reserva Natural Ouroborus Galilea Gastronomía La Vuelta al Mundo